Guide to the University Career Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Pre-medical, fellowship program, and Junior Year Abroad records, 1980-1986; Accession 1987-A-110
  - Fellowship Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 612)
    - Dorot Fellowship, 1983-1984
      - Chronological file (Box 8, Folder 719)
      - Staff meeting notes (Box 8, Folder 720)
      - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 721)
      - Booklets requested (Box 8, Folder 722)
      - Requisitions (Box 8, Folder 723)
      - Memoranda (Box 8, Folder 724)
    - ASME (American Society of Magazine Editors), 1983-1984
      - Basic information (Box 8, Folder 725)
      - Correspondence and Papers (Box 8, Folder 726 - 727)
      - Forms (Box 8, Folder 728)
      - Memoranda (Box 8, Folder 729)
      - Applicants
      - Algorithms (Box 8, Folder 741 - 742)
      - Applicants: lists (Box 8, Folder 743)
      - Bulletin and Calendar, Information sheets (original) (Box 8, Folder 744)
      - Committees (Box 8, Folder 745)
      - Masters-Fellowships (old) (Box 8, Folder 746)
      - Spring Reception and Invitation List (Box 8, Folder 747)
    - Fulbright Program, 1983-1984
      - Algorithm (Box 8, Folder 748)
      - Basic information (Box 8, Folder 749)
      - Committee papers (Box 8, Folder 750)
      - Correspondence: incoming and outgoing (Box 8, Folder 751 - 752)
      - Catalog (Box 8, Folder 753)
      - Forms (Box 8, Folder 754)
      - Form 1 copies A-J, K-Z (Box 8, Folder 755 - 756)
      - Form 8 originals (Box 8, Folder 757)
      - Losers (Box 8, Folder 758)
      - Committee members (Box 8, Folder 759)
      - Memoranda (Box 8, Folder 760)
      - National recommendations (Box 8, Folder 761)
      - Tic sheets (Box 8, Folder 762)
      - Winners (Box 8, Folder 763)
    - Light Fellowship, 1983-1984
      - Basic information (Box 8, Folder 764)
      - Correspondence and Papers (Box 8, Folder 765)
      - Committee members (Box 8, Folder 766)
      - Forms (Box 8, Folder 767)
      - Memoranda (Box 8, Folder 768)
      - Applicants
    - Luce Scholars Program, 1983-1984
      - Basic information (Box 9, Folder 778)
      - Correspondence and Papers (Box 9, Folder 779)
      - Committee members (Box 9, Folder 780)
      - Forms (Box 9, Folder 781)
      - Memoranda (Box 9, Folder 782)
      - Applicants
    - Marshall Scholarship, 1983-1984
      - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 801)
      - Incoming Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 802)
      - Forms (Box 9, Folder 803)
      - Memoranda (Box 9, Folder 804)
    - Mellon: Basic information, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 805)
    - NSF (National Science Foundation), 1983-1984
      - Basic information (Box 9, Folder 806)
      - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 807)
      - Forms (Box 9, Folder 808)
    - New York Times, 1984
      - Basic information (Box 9, Folder 809)
      - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 810)
      - Applicants
    - Rhodes Scholarship, 1983-1984
      - Basic information (Box 9, Folder 823)
      - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 824)
      - Forms (Box 9, Folder 825)
      - Memoranda (Box 9, Folder 826)
    - St. Andrew"s Society Scholarship, 1983-1984
      - Basic information (Box 9, Folder 827)
      - Correspondence and Papers (Box 9, Folder 828 - 829)
      - Committee members (Box 9, Folder 830)
      - Memoranda (Box 9, Folder 831)
      - Applicants
    - Time Program, 1984
      - Basic information (Box 9, Folder 834)
      - Correspondence and Papers (Box 9, Folder 835 - 836)
      - Forms (Box 9, Folder 837)
      - Committee members (Box 9, Folder 838)
      - Memoranda (Box 9, Folder 839)
      - Applicants
    - Truman Scholarship, 1983-1984
      - Basic information (Box 9, Folder 855)
      - Correspondence and Papers (Box 9, Folder 856 - 857)
      - Forms (Box 9, Folder 858)
      - Committee members (Box 9, Folder 859)
      - Memoranda (Box 9, Folder 860)
      - Applicants
    - Yale-China Association: Information, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 871)
    - Yale-GM (General Motors), 1983-1984
      - Applicants
    - Incomplete applications (Box 9, Folder 908)
  - Pre-Med File, 1983-1984
    - Special Category
    - Applicants: Inactive
    - Applicants: Special Category, Inactive
      - Yellow Cards (Box 12, Folder 1092)
- Junior Year Abroad records, 1983-1985; Accession 1988-A-046
  - Class of 1983
    - Missing (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - incomplete applications (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Class of 1984
    - incomplete applications (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Class of 1985
- Junior Year Abroad student records, 1987; Accession 1988-A-062
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - Withdrawn
  - Withdrawn
- Pre-medical student records, 1976-1984; Accession 1988-A-075
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - CLASS OF 1984
    - SPECIAL CATEGORY
    - INCOMPLETES
    - INCOMPLETES SPECIAL CATEGORY (Box 3)
  - SCHOOL BOOK 1984 (A listing of which students applied to which schools) (Box 3)
  - YALE UNIVERSITY HEALTH PROFESSIONS ADVISORY COMMITTEE PREMEDICAL RECORD CARDS A-Z (not necessarily in alphabetical order - same information to be found in folders) Where a folder exists for a student his/her card is in it. (Box 3)
- Records concerning fellowship programs, 1985-1986; Accession 1989-A-005
  - Bulletin and Calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Posters, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Poster Masters, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Data Entry for New Fellowships (Alphabetical by Granting Agency), 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Algorithms, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fellowship Calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Fellowship Application Masters, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fellowship Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Fellowship Committees, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fellowship Correspondence - General, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sample Copies of Committee Letters, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fellowship Guide, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Fellowship Reception, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Expense Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mail Receipts, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Tic Sheets, 1985-1986
    - ASME, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Blanning, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Carey, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Carnegie Endowment, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Churchill, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Collaborative, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - DAAD, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Dorot, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Fulbright, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Huang, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Luce, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - NCAA, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - N.Y. Times Editorial, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - N.Y. Times Summer Minority, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - St. Andrew"s, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Time, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Truman, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Yale - Studies in the Environment, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Zion, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Fellowship Tic Sheets -, Spring 1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Fulbright Tic Sheet -, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Fellowship Tic Sheets -, Fall 1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - ASME, 1985-1986
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Student"s Name
  - ASME Committee, 1985-1986
  - BLANNING, 1985-1986
    - Contract, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Student"s Name
    - Wendy Blanning Memorial Summer Fellowship, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - CAREY, 1985-1986
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - CAREY Scholarship Committee, 1985-1986
    - Student"s Name
  - CARNEGIE ENDOWMENT, 1985-1986
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Internship Applications, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Student"s Name
  - CHURCHILL, 1985-1986
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Student"s Name
  - CIEE General Information, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - ISIC, 2nd Copy:, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Student"s Name
  - CIEE, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - ISIC, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
    - Student"s Name
  - COLLABORATIVE FULBRIGHT, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Student"s Name
  - DAAD, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - DAAD Committee:, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Student"s Name
  - DOROT:
    - Agreements, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Forms -, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Travel Grant Tic Sheet, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Basic Information, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda -, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 153)
      - Travel Grant Recipients (in folder 147), 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 156)
      - Contracts/Acceptance Letters/Check Receipts, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Student"s Name
  - FULBRIGHT, 1985-1986
    - Fulbright Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - Fulbright Committee:, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - Losers, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - Winners, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 179)
    - Fulbright Manual, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - Fulbright candidates that withdrew from competition, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 182)
    - Fulbright Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - Additional Fulbright Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - Fulbright Statistics, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 187)
    - Fulbright National Recommendations, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - Fulbright Not Recommended, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - Fulbright Copies, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - INPO, 1985-1986
    - INPO Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - INPO Scholarship, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - KEASBEY, 1985-1986
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Keasbey Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Information, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Student"s Name
  - LUCE, 1985-1986
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 256)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 257)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 258)
    - Luce Committee Ratings, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 259)
    - Luce Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 260)
    - Luce Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 265)
    - Student"s Name
  - MARSHALL, 1986-1987
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 285)
  - MELLON, 1985-1986
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 286)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 287)
  - NATIONAL SCIENCE FOUNDATION, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 289)
  - NCAA, 1985-1986
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 290)
    - NCAA Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 291)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 292)
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 293)
    - Applications, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 294)
    - NCAA Basketball:, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 295)
    - Student"s Name
  - N.Y. TIMES EDITORIAL
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 300)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 301)
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 302)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 303)
    - N.Y. Times Edit, Ass"t Committee:, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 304)
    - Student"s Name
  - N.Y. TIMES SUMMER MINORITY INTERNSHIP, 1985-1986
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 316)
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 317)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 318)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 319)
    - Student"s Name
  - RHODES, 1985-1986
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - ST. ANDREW"S, 1985-1986
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 328)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 329)
    - St. Andrew"s Committee:, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 330)
    - St. Andrew"s Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 334)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 335)
    - Student"s Name
  - TIME, INC., 1985-1986
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 340)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 341)
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 342)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 343)
    - Student"s Name
      - Time, Inc. Summer Internship Committee:, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 345)
      - Time College Achievement Awards, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 360)
  - TRUMAN MEMORIAL SCHOLARSHIP, 1985-1986
    - Truman Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 361)
    - Truman Committee:, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 362)
    - Truman Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 367)
    - Truman Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 368)
    - Truman Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 369)
    - Student"s Name, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
      - Truman Scholarships, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 384)
  - YALE STUDIES IN THE ENVIRONMENT, 1985-1986
    - Basic Information, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 385)
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 386)
    - Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 387)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 388)
    - Student"s Name
- Pre-medical student records, 1985-1986; Accession 1989-A-091
  - PREMED APPLICANTS FOR THE CLASS OF 1985
  - SPECIAL CATEGORY FOR THE CLASS OF 1985
  - INCOMPLETES
    - Premed School Applicants for the Class of 1985 (recommendations or blue cards)
  - SPECIAL CATEGORY FOR THE CLASS OF 1985 (recommendations or blue cards)
  - CLASS OF 1986
  - YELLOW CARDS ONLY [The following premed files had only transcripts and MDC (files destroyed)]
    - Class of 1985, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 287)
  - CLASS OF 1986
  - Special Category 1986
  - CLASS OF 1986 INCOMPLETES (recommendations or blue cards in file)
  - Incompletes, Special Category, Class of 1986
  - The following files had only transcripts and MDC (files destroyed)
    - Special Category and Class of 1986
- Fellowship program student records, 1986-1987; Accession 1990-A-006
  - ASME
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - BEINECKE
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - BLANNING
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - CAREY
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Date of Graduation, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - CARNEGIE ENDOWMENT
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - CHURCHILL
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - CIEE
    - Basic Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - COLLABORATIVE RESEARCH GRANTS
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - DAAD
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Sample Committee Folder, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Date of Graduation, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - DACOR
    - General Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - DOROT
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Reception Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Applicatnts, 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - No Fulbright to New York Times Summer Minority, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - FULBRIGRT
    - General Information, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Campus Interview Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Additional Fulbright Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Winner, Loser, Alternate, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Recommended, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Not Recommended, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Campus Rating Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Copies of Applications, Forms 1 and 8, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 116 - 117)
  - GOVERNOR OF OHIO INTERNSHIP
    - Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - LEADERSHIP AMERICA
    - General Information, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Basic Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - LUCE
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - MARSHALL
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - MELLON
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - NCAA
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - NEW YORK TIMES EDITORIAL - INTERNSHIP
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 194)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 195)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - NEW YORK TIMES SUMMER MINORITY
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 203)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 204)
    - Committee Date of Graduation, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - NEW YORK TIMES WASHINGTON CLERKSHIP
  - RHODES
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - ST. ANDREW"S
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - Date of Graduation, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - TIME
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - TRUMAN
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 249)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 250)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - YALE- BROOKINGS
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 275)
    - Applicants, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 276)
  - YALE CLUB OF PRINCETON PRIZE
    - General Information, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 291)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 293)
    - Did not Apply:, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - YALE- ILGWU
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - YALE-PUBLIC DEFENDER SERVICE
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 331)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 332)
    - Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 333)
    - Did Not Apply:, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 352)
  - YALE-STUDIES IN THE ENVIRONMENT
    - Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 355)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 356)
  - ZION
    - Basic Information, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 372)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 373)
  - FELLOWSHIPS GENERAL
    - Fellowship Correspondence General, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 374)
    - Fellowship Deadlines (Master and Forms), 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 375)
    - Fellowship - General Information, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Fellowships for Seniors, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 377)
    - Fellowship Inserts for Guides, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 378)
    - Fellowship Guide, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 379)
    - Fellowship Reception, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 380)
    - Guest List for Fellowship Reception, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 381)
    - Updated Committee Members, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 382)
    - Poster Masters, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 383)
    - Fellowship Committee Letters, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 384)
    - Updated Committee Members w/ Salutations, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 385)
    - Fellowship Committees, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 386)
    - Fellowship Committees, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 387)
- Fellowship records, circa 1987-1988; Accession 1991-A-030
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
  - GENERAL FELLOWSHIP
    - General Fellowship Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Fellowship Program Calendar, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Fellowship Guide Insert (Master), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Fellowships for Seniors Sheet (Master), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Fellowship Guide Revisions (Part II), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Fellowship Brochure for Juniors, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Information Sheets (Masters), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Fellowship Committees Final Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Fellowship Committee Invitation Letters, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Fellowship Committee Member Selection, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Posters, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Poster Masters, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Fellowship Reception Guest List, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - BEINECKE MEMORIAL SCHOLARSHIP PROGRAM:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - WENDY E. BLANNING MEMORIAL SUMMER FELLOWSHIP:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - JOHN L. CAREY SCHOLARSHIP:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - CARNEGIE ENDOWMENT STUDENT INTERN PROGRAM:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - WINSTON CHURCHILL FOUNDATION SCHOLARSHIPS:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - CIEE ISIC SCHOLARSHIPS:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - COLLABORATIVE RESEARCH GRANTS:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 73)